allfungirlsgames.com 2016-02-09

# AllFunGirlsGames.com Privacy Policy

At AllFunGirlsGames.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by AllFunGirlsGames.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, AllFunGirlsGames.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

AllFunGirlsGames.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on AllFunGirlsGames.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

AllFunGirlsGames.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. AllFunGirlsGames.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

### 3rd-Party Advertisemsents

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

### Site Privacy Policy Modifications

AllFunGirlsGames.com will from time to time review and revise this privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this website. AllFunGirlsGames.com has the right to change our privacy practices without prior notice. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.
